<!--
  #%L
  GwtMaterial
  %%
  Copyright (C) 2015 - 2016 GwtMaterialDesign
  %%
  Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  You may obtain a copy of the License at
  
       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  
  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  limitations under the License.
  #L%
  -->
<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
             xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
             xmlns:m="urn:import:gwt.material.design.client.ui"
             xmlns:m.html="urn:import:gwt.material.design.client.ui.html"
             xmlns:demo="urn:import:gwt.material.design.demo.client.ui">
  <m:MaterialPanel>
    <m:MaterialRow addStyleNames="code">
      <m:MaterialTitle title="isSupported()" description="Will check if the Notification API is supported"/>
      <demo:PrettyPre addStyleNames="lang-java">
        PwaManager.isPwaSupported()
      </demo:PrettyPre>
    </m:MaterialRow>

    <m:MaterialRow addStyleNames="code">
      <m:MaterialTitle title="Request Permission" />
      <m:MaterialButton ui:field="requestPermission" text="Request Permission" />
      <demo:PrettyPre addStyleNames="lang-java">
        // Will return the following status (see next section) <br/>
        Notification.getPermission();
      </demo:PrettyPre>
    </m:MaterialRow>

    <m:MaterialRow addStyleNames="code">
      <m:MaterialTitle title="Permission Status"/>
      <g:HTMLPanel>
        <blockquote>
          <p><b>denied</b> - The user refuses to have notifications displayed. </p>
          <p><b>granted</b> - The user accepts having notifications displayed. </p>
          <p><b>default</b> - The user choice is unknown and therefore the browser will act as if the value were denied. </p>
        </blockquote>
      </g:HTMLPanel>
    </m:MaterialRow>

    <m:MaterialRow addStyleNames="code">
      <m:MaterialTitle title="Show Notification" />
      <m:MaterialButton ui:field="notify" text="Show Notification"/>
    </m:MaterialRow>

    <m:MaterialRow addStyleNames="code">
      <m:MaterialTitle title="Notification Options" />
      <g:HTMLPanel>
        <blockquote>
          <p><b>actions</b> - The actions array of the notification as specified in the options parameter of the constructor.</p>
          <p><b>badge</b> - The URL of the image used to represent the notification when there is not enough space to display the notification itself.</p>
          <p><b>body</b> - The body string of the notification as specified in the options parameter of the constructor.</p>
          <p><b>data</b> - Returns a structured clone of the notification’s data.</p>
          <p><b>dir</b> - The text direction of the notification as specified in the options parameter of the constructor.</p>
          <p><b>lang</b> - The language code of the notification as specified in the options parameter of the constructor. </p>
          <p><b>tag</b> - The ID of the notification (if any) as specified in the options parameter of the constructor. </p>
          <p><b>icon</b> - The URL of the image used as an icon of the notification as specified in the options parameter of the constructor. </p>
          <p><b>image</b> - The  URL of an image to be displayed as part of the notification, as specified in the options parameter of the constructor. </p>
          <p><b>renotify</b> - Specifies whether the user should be notified after a new notification replaces an old one. </p>
          <p><b>requireInteraction</b> - A Boolean indicating that a notification should remain active until the user clicks or dismisses it, rather than closing automatically. </p>
          <p><b>silent</b> - Specifies whether the notification should be silent, i.e. no sounds or vibrations should be issued, regardless of the device settings. </p>
          <p><b>timestamp</b> - Specifies the time at which a notification is created or applicable (past, present, or future). </p>
          <p><b>title</b> - The title of the notification as specified in the first parameter of the constructor. </p>
          <p><b>vibrate</b> - Specifies a vibration pattern for devices with vibration hardware to emit. </p>
        </blockquote>
      </g:HTMLPanel>
    </m:MaterialRow>

    <m:MaterialRow addStyleNames="code">
      <m:MaterialTitle title="Notification Handlers" />
      <demo:PrettyPre addStyleNames="lang-java">
        Notification notification = new Notification("GMD Says", options); <br/>
        // Listen to any Notification events <br/>
        // A handler for the click event. It is triggered each time the user clicks on the notification. <br/>
        notification.setOnclick(param1 -> MaterialToast.fireToast("Clicked")); <br/>
        // A handler for the close event. It is triggered when the user closes the notification. <br/>
        notification.setOnclose(param1 -> MaterialToast.fireToast("Closed")); <br/>
        // A handler for the error event. It is triggered each time the notification encounters an error. <br/>
        notification.setOnerror(param1 -> MaterialToast.fireToast("Error")); <br/>
        // A handler for the show event. It is triggered when the notification is displayed. <br/>
        notification.setOnshow(param1 -> MaterialToast.fireToast("Shown")); <br/>
      </demo:PrettyPre>
    </m:MaterialRow>
  </m:MaterialPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>
